A Guide to Arena Stage Financial Documents and Projects, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage Financial Documents and Projects
  - Royalties: Banko Dancing (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: A lie of the Mind (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: On the Town (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Vivisections From the Blown Mind (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: A Walk in the Woods (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: On the Way home (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: The Glass Managerie (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: A Midsummers Night's Dream (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: The Man Who Came to Dinner (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Stand-up Tragedy (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Merrily We Roll Along (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Banjo Dancing (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Coconuts (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Heart Break House (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: The Crucible (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Banjo Dancing (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Suzuki (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Abyssinia (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Six Characters in Search of an Author (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Nothing Sacred (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: The Fool Show (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Playboy of the West Indies (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Ring Round the Moon (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Briar Patch (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Judevine (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: A Chorus of Disapproval (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: A Doll House (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Juno and Paycock (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Fences (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: On the way Home (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Montieth and Rand (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Conquest of the South Pole (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Karamozov Brothers (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Bette and Boo (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: The Piggy Bank (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Crime and Punishment (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Glenngarry, Glen Ross (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Ourselves Alone (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: King's Men (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Light up the Sky (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Enrico IV (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Cherry Orchard (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Les Blancs (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: The Immigrant (Box Box 27)
  - Play Labs financial information, 1987-1988 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: American Splendor (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Joe Turner's Come and Gone (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Rives/Ravines (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Checkmates (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Emlyn William's Dylan Thomas Growing Up (Box Box 27)
  - production costs for "The 1940's Radio Hour" (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties and production costs: The Regard of Flight (Box Box 27)
  - Misc. royalties: 1985-1986 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Banjo Dancing (Box Box 27)
  - royalties and production costs: Beehive (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: 1968-1968 season (Box Box 27)
  - royalties: 1969-1970 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties gen. 1970-1971 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties gen. 1971-1972 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties and gen costs: Moonchildren (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: Raisin (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties gen. 1972-1973 (Box Box 27)
  - "The New Theater" costs (Box Box 27)
  - royalties: Horatio (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: 1956-1957 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties gen., 1965-1966 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties gen: 1966-1967 (Box Box 27)
  - general Royalties: 1967-1968 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties 1961-1962 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: 1962-1963 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties 1963-1964 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties 1964-1965 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: 1957-1958 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties:1958-1959 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: 1959-1960 (Box Box 27)
  - Royalties: 1960-1961 (Box Box 27)